<nixmashuplinks>
    <nixmashuplink>
        <id>581</id>
        <title>In Praise of the JVM</title>
        <linkurl>
            http://zeroturnaround.com/rebellabs/5-reasons-the-jvm-development-tools-market-rocks/
        </linkurl>
        <linktext>
            Five reasons why, according to Rebel Labs, that the Java Virtual Machine is so awesome
            for developers. A fresh yet mature set of technologies, established standards and
            "good-enough" practices, an abundance of JVM technologies spread across commercial and
            open source spaces, risk-free experimentation for developers, and an enormous,
            influential and active community.
        </linktext>
        <tags>java|development|career</tags>
        <postdate>November 2, 2014</postdate>
        <season>fall</season>
        <linkimage>IMG1012015</linkimage>
    </nixmashuplink>
    <nixmashuplink>
        <id>580</id>
        <title>Lowe's Newest Robotic Employee</title>
        <linkurl>http://youtu.be/Sp9176vm7Co</linkurl>
        <linktext>
            Lowe's has a new Autonomous Retail Service Robot they're testing at their San Jose
            Midtown store. The OSHbot as it is called (for Orchard Supply Hardware) will be "helping
            customers navigate the store and associates work more effectively." That is, as long as
            there's a need for associates...
        </linktext>
        <tags>futuretech|robotics|trends</tags>
        <postdate>November 2, 2014</postdate>
        <season>fall</season>
        <linkimage>IMG1012014</linkimage>
    </nixmashuplink>
    <nixmashuplink>
        <id>579</id>
        <title>Driverless Car Stats, Figures and Features</title>
        <linkurl>http://www.fix.com/blog/driverless-car-revolution/</linkurl>
        <linktext>
            Several infographics with statistics and information about Google's Driverless Car along
            with a 3 minute video of people taking their first ride in it. Looked pretty great.
        </linktext>
        <tags>selfdrivingcars|futuretech</tags>
        <postdate>November 2, 2014</postdate>
        <season>fall</season>
        <linkimage>IMG101101015</linkimage>
    </nixmashuplink>
    <nixmashuplink>
        <id>578</id>
        <title>Grocery Shopping with Glass</title>
        <linkurl>http://youtu.be/TkfF-WGUisw</linkurl>
        <linktext>
            This is a very fun video of a man doing his grocery shopping with Google Glass, from the
            perspective of the wearer. Purchase list displayed and checked off, with prices
            subtracted from his shopping budget, ingredient lookup, coupon retrieval and a quick
            video call to his wife who sees the yogurt selections through his glasses.
        </linktext>
        <tags>futuretech|wearables|youtube</tags>
        <postdate>November 2, 2014</postdate>
        <season>fall</season>
        <linkimage>P10100093</linkimage>
    </nixmashuplink>
</nixmashuplinks>
